Guide to the Horizons Theater Company records, 1972-2015 MS2371
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Promotional materials, 1972-2015; 1980-2007; MS2371 Series 4; 8 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series include advertisements, programs, newsletters, photographs, photographic slides, posters, A/V materials, newspaper clippings, articles, play reviews, and press releases. The material dates from approximately 1972-2015.
  - Washington Area Feminist Theater, Circa 1972; Series 4 (Map-folder 1, Item 1)
  - Reviews Mother May 1, 1978; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mother, May I First Ed: Spring 78 2nd Ed: Summer and Fall 78, 1978; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Articles - Pro Femina, 1978-1980; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Reviews, 1978-1980; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Motherhouses Jan '79, 1978-1981; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - PFT - Institutional Promo, 1978-1985; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Photos (Head Shots) of Company Members, 1978-1980; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Promo - Pro Femina and Horizons, 1978-1993; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Flyer Motherhouses, 1979; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reviews - Motherhouse, 1979; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cartoons - It's About Time..., 1979; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - It's About Time - Reviews, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Unicorn Times "A Theater for, and of, Women", 1979; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Press/Publicity File, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Reviews - An I For You, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Trip to Copenhagen, Dk. An I for You Spring '80, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Promo - Pro Femina, 1980-1982; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Pro-Femina, 1980-1983; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Printing Rate Cards, 1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Reviews/Fertility Rites, 1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Fertility Rites, 1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Close Calls/Promo, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Close Calls/Far Cries Reviews, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Close Calls/Far Cries Fall '81, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Booking Packets, 1981-1984; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - PR 84-85 Season, 1981-1985; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - March 27th - Offic on Aging Booking, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Leslie's File Personal Things [Motherhouses: Bookings], 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - It's Our Turn Flyers/Programs Promo, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Lion's Cage Promo, etc., 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Write/Press Packets TV and Radio/Press to Contact, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ads in Local Newspapers, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Flyer/Letter/Program Marking Time Info, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Radio/TV PR Marking Time, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Jumble Sale, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Marking Time Reviews and Copies, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - P.S.A. and Calls, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Marking Time P.R., 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Profemina Theatre's Special Preview Press Opening, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - P.R. 2nd, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Touring/Bookings Marking Time, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Marking Time Photos, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - E Diggs Reviews, 1982; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Press Packet, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Pro Femina - Publicity, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Promo - Name Change, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Close Ties Photos, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Close Ties Flyers and Programs, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Close Ties Opening - Mailing List, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Promo - Close Ties, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Close Ties any P.R. Stuff, 1983; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Reviews - Close Ties, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Bookings Women's Work, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Promo - Women's Work, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Women's Work/Program Insert/Rough Draft of Program, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Press Pt front Women's Work, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 2nd Press Releases and P.T.A. Women's Work, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Reviews of Women's Work '83, 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Close Ties, 1983-1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Women's Work - Reviews and Events, 1983-1986; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Promo - Pro Femina and Horizons materials, 1983-1988; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Promo - Programs, 1983-2000; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Rickie Orchen Invite, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Sisterfire, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Georgetowner Feature June, 1984, Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - On Stage P.R., 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - How it Played 1985, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Suite Life Info, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Promo - Signs of Life, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Joan Schenkar, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Discussion Questionnaires, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Signs of Life Reviews, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Signs of Life, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Horizons - Top Girls, 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Beth Joselow Wed. Nov. 7th, 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Talking With, 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Talking With (1st Press Release), 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Talking With, 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases - Talking With, 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - PSA Orgasmo Adulto, 1984; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Orgasmo PR, 1984-1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Reviews Orgasmo Audulto, 1984-1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Suite Life event for the League of Washington Theaters, 1984; Series 4 (Map-folder 1, Item 2)
  - Women's Work Gala/Women's History Week, 1984-1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Expanding Season, 1984-1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sample Press Releases, 1984-1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Bravo Award First, 1984-1986; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Promo - Horizons Production History, 1984-1988; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Reviews - Orgasmo, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - S.L. Piece on Booklet, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Bravo Award Press Release, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Bravo Reactions, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - What the Critics Say, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - New Voices '85, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - New Voices, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - "New Voices" - Press Releases, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Horizons Logo Stat, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Guide Bill, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Advertising, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Last Days - Reviews, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Last Days - Reviews, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Last Days..., 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Washington Post Proofs, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Miss Lulu Reviews, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Miss Lulu P.R., 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Women's Work in NY Press Release, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Women's Work Fundraiser, 1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Horizons "Theater from a Woman's Perspective" Pamphlets, 1985; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Horizons Publicity, 1985; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Play Reading/Outside Waco Feb. '85, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Reviews Johnny Bull, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Reviews - "Johnny Bull", 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Press Release - "Johnny Bull", 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Johnny Bull, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Johnny Bull Press Releases, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Programs etc. Info - Charabac, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Overview Reviews, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Estelle Parsons/Women's Studio Workshop, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - The Female Entertainer - Fall Show, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - The Female Entertainer Reviews, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - ...The House - Reviews, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - This is the House, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Photos - "Automatic Pilot" Playwright Info, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Reviews - Automatic Pilot, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Automatic Pilot, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Pre-Season 86/87 Review/Post, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Spotlight Leslie J/Washingtonian Horizons Success Review June 86, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Marking Time Advertising Forms, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Brava 86 Reviews and Photos, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Brava 86 Raffle, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Bravo 86 Press Release, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Promo-Radiothon '86, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Horizons Brochure 86, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Subscriber Brochure 86/87, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Absent-Minded Sweethearts, 1986; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Sample P.S.A.s, 1986-1988; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - PR Materials, 1986-1988; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Brava Awards Press Releases, 1986-1988; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Promo-Horizons Reviews, 1986-1995; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Promo - Robert Prosky, 1986-1998; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. California Press Release, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Mrs. California Reviews, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Guide to the Lively Arts Mrs. California, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Reviews - Mrs. California, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Reviews, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases A.M.S., 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - A.M.S. |S.L| Reviews '87, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Reviews: Still Life '87, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Still Life - Veterans Performance Article, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Roy Barber - AMS, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - AMS/SL Guide to the Lively Arts, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - AMS/SL - Press Releases/PSA's, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - AMS/SL P.S.A., 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Press Release for Marathon, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Promo - Marathon '33, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Marathon 33, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Marathon Reviews Misc., 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Marathon P.S.A., 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Marathon Reviews Post/City Paper/Times/WTOP, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Promo-Horizons, 1987-1988 Season, Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Staff Photo 87-Fall, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Awards '87, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Horizons Advertisements, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Management Handbook - etc articles, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Female Perspective Symposium Article, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Raffle, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Birthday Party, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Entertainment Advertiser's Agreeement, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Marketing "Alice", 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Promo - Alice, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Alice Press Release, 1987; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Alice Reviews Times - City Paper - Journal, 1987; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - A My Name is Alice 2nd Press Release, 1987; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Alice Proofs, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Reviews A... My Name is Alice, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Promo-Alice, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Promo-Awards Material, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Washington Harbor Restaurant '88, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Ad. and Admission Card, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Promo-Publicity Clips, 1987-1998; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Scheherazade-Press Release, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Scheherazade Reviews Georgetowner-Times-CP-Post, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Sch Panel Discussion, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Promo-Scheherazade, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Scheherazade - Playwright - Past, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Mothers Day Luncheon, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Mothers Day, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases and Ads - Eleemosynary, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Magazine/Articles/Travel Guides/Ellemosynary, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Eleemosynary, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Eleemosynary Press Release, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Reviews - Eleemosynary, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Alice - Ads, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Old Reviews of Alice, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Alice Ad - Georgetown '88, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Alice Namesake Night/88, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Alice Flyers, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Alice is Back - Reviewers Quote Sheet, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Alice is Back Proofs Washington Post, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - P.S.A., 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - WGMs Alice Ad copy - Alice is Back, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Press List Alice is Back, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - July 31st, 1988; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Alice is Back Reviews, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Alice 100th Performance, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - A My Name is Alice and Your Maybe 10, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Alice is Back - Post Advertising, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Alice, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Alice is Back Reviews, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Alice is Back/Your Back, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Alice is Back - Promos, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - P.S.A., 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 3 Postcards, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Horizons - 3 Postcards Flyers, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Three Post Cards, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 3 Postcards, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - 3 Postcards Reviews, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Three Postcards Reviews, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Promo-Three Postcards, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - 3 Postcards Press Release, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - 3 Postcards Press Release, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Touring '88, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Touring/Special Performances, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Workshop, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - AT&T Grant Press Release, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - 1st International Women Playwrights Conference Oct. 88, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Horizons Counts Successes Article 88, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - City Stage Article: Acting Tim O'Brien, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Monthly Ads, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Space/Articles, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Helen Hayes Awards Reviews, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Brava Negatives, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Brava Brochure, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Brava Benefit Committee, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Brava Awards, 1988; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Brava, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Herbs, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Herbs Bash Press Release, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Herb's Winter Cast Bash, 1988-1990; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Reckless-Advertising for Program, 1988-1990; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Horizons-Promotional Materials, 1988-1990; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Reckless Reviews (Quotes), 1988-1990; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "On the Horizon", 1988-1993; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Horizons Theater - Selected Reviews and Newsletters, 1988-1999; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases for Pump Boys, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Pumpboys and Dinettes, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Pump Boys, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Pump Boys Reviews, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Pump Boys, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Pump Boys, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Pump Boys, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Pump Boys Radio, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Stick Wife Press Release, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Stick Wife, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Stick Wife, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Stick Wife/Brava Backstage Article, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Stick Wife, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - The Stick Wife, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Stick Wife Reviews, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Seasonal Press Release August 31st '89, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Place Ads for Intowner Jewish Week, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Radio Stations Ticket Give Aways, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Promo-Special Events, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Robert Prosky, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Helen Hayes Backstage Review, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Promo-Helen Hayes Awards, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Backstage Article on Leslie, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Season Press Release, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Bravo Paper, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Bravo Press Release Herb White, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Bravo - Herb White, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Bravo - Articles on Herb, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Bravo - Invites, 1989; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Horizons Promo Material, 1989-2006; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Reckless, 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Reckless Program, 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Reckless Poster, Flyers and Cards, 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Reckless Press Release P.S.A., 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Reckless Press Release P.S.A., 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Reckless, 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Telemarketing, 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Special Events Rush Drafts, 1990; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sylvia's Real Good Advice, 1993; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Interview - Developing and Directing Plays by Women, 1993; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - "On The Horizon", 1994-1997; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Professional Reviews and Features, 1995; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Promo-Horizons Newsclippings, 1995-2001; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Deb Margolin - Reviews, 1996-1997; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Gail Clips, 1997-1998; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Promo-Theater Publications, 1997-1998; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Gail Clips, 1997-1998; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Promo-Newsletters and Articles, 1997-2000; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Promo-"On The Horizon", 1999; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Good PR for Copying, 1999; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Readings, 1999; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Promo - I Want to Tell You, 2001; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Press Lists, Undated; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Stationary Old, Undated; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Raffle (Gala), Undated; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Raffles - Ideas, Undated; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Promo-Photos, Undated; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Posters, 1987-1990; Series 4; 1.5 Linear Feet (Box 40)
  - Promo-It's About Time, 1979-1981; Series 4 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Promo-Pro Femina and Horizons, 1980-1987; Series 4 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Promo-Pro Femina and Horizons, 1981-1989; Series 4 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Flyers/Programs It's Our Turn, 1982; Series 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Promo-Keely and Du Flyer, 1993; Series 4 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Promo-Horizons, 1995; Series 4 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Pro Femina Theatre program, circa 1970s-early 1980s; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - The Amateur: Reflections of Zelda, Washington Area Feminist Theatre, with production notes, circa 1970s; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Productions [miscellaneous promotional materials] [1/2], 1988, 1994, 1996-2001, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Productions [miscellaneous promotional materials] [2/2], 1988, 1994, 1996-2001, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Tea, at the Smithsonian Institution, 1993 May 7; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 1993 Season: Tea, and Sylvia's Real Good Advice, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - 1993-1994 Performances, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - On the Horizon Newsletters, 1993, 1994, 1997, 1999, 2001, 2003; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Young Playwright's Festival, 1994-1995; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - 1994-1995 Productions, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Horizons/Jewish Community Center of Northern Virginia, 1994-1995, 1998; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Reviews from the mid-1990s [1/2], 1994-1995, 1997, 2001; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Reviews from the mid-1990s [2/2], 1994-1995, 1997, 2001; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Kindertransport 1995, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Press and other materials from In Good Company, 1997 December; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Dear Esther, 1997, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous press, 1997, 1998, 2000; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Helen Hays Awards, 1997, 1999; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Reviews of Dear Esther, 1998; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - 1998-1999 Season, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - In Good Company [various editions], 1998-1999, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - 1999-2000 Season, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Game Show-Press, 2000; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - In Good Company, The Kosher Edition, 2000; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - The Last Game Show, 2000; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - LGS, March 1-April 1, 2000 [The Last Game Show], MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Press & Reviews 2000-02, 2000, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Dar Williams, 2001 February 12; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - 2002-Season [1/2[, 2001, 2002, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - 2002-Season [Hot & Bothered] [1/2], 2001, 2002, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - One of the Few, 2001; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Hot and Bothered, 2001, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - I Want to Tell You, 2001, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Three Roses, 2001, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Icons 2002 [In Good Company: Sexual Icons], MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Losing Lawrence, 2002, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Performance Agreement and information from The Old Post Office Pavilion, 2002, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Losing Lawrence 2002, 2002, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Losing Lawrence, Ovaries, Sexual Icons, Mat'ls, 2002-2003, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 2002-2003 Season, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 4)